[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who found and named  the first Homo Erectus in 1891?", "correct_answer": "Eugene Dubois", "incorrect_answers": ["Franz Boas", "Louis and Mary Leakey", "David Johannson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do elephants protect their skin from the aggressive UV-radiation?", "correct_answer": "By wallowing in mud", "incorrect_answers": ["By wallowing in their own feces", "By hiding in the shadow of thick branches", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Pretty Woman, this character, portrayed by Julia Roberts, is a prostitute who meets Edward Lewis, after he asks her for directions.", "correct_answer": "Vivian Ward", "incorrect_answers": ["Vivian Vance", "Vivian Brandt", "Vivian Tyler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is Sector 7 according to the movie Transformers?", "correct_answer": "In the Hoover Dam", "incorrect_answers": ["Under the Empire State Building", "In Mount Rushmore", "Under the White House"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are just 2 species of turkey in the world.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie, set in New York City, was written by Calogero Lorenzo Palminteri and directed by Robert De Niro?", "correct_answer": "A Bronx Tale - 1993", "incorrect_answers": ["Mad Dog and Glory - 1993", "This Boys Life - 1993", "Heat - 1995"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It has been estimated that in Australia, there are about twice as many kangaroos as there are people.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which late-night television host is famous for his amusing Top Ten lists?", "correct_answer": "David Letterman", "incorrect_answers": ["Conan OBrien", "Craig Ferguson", "Jay Leno"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What EU country first discovered the therapeutic powers of yogurt?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "England", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1995 this person addressed the UN General Assembly in English, French, Spanish, Arabic, Chinese  and Russian.", "correct_answer": "Pope John Paul II", "incorrect_answers": ["Mother Teresa", "Yuri Andropov", "Fidel Castro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What place did the 2008 movie Iron Man have on the list of all time best opening weekends when it first came out?", "correct_answer": "10th", "incorrect_answers": ["11th", "9th", "8th"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the  first museum in the USA located?", "correct_answer": "Charleston, S.C.", "incorrect_answers": ["Philadelphia, PA.", "Boston, MA.", "Augusta, Maine"]}]